# Mona Shaban Frontend Developer

mona00mona1997@gmail.com

+972599923814

in Mona Mohammed

Rafah, Palestine

**★** Portfolio

Mona Mohammed

## **ABOUT ME**

I am a highly skilled Frontend Developer specializing in React.js.

My expertise lies in building reusable and flexible components and integrating APIs.

I am always passionate about learning and undertaking new challenges, constantly evolving, and enjoying dealing with problems and providing optimal

I look forward to an opportunity where I can exploit my skills and further develop them, I have the capability and confidence to work independently or within a team.

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### 02/2023 - 09/2023

## Gaza, Palestine

### 03/2023 - 03/2023

### Saudi Arabia

## 02/2023 - 02/2023

## Gaza, Palestine

### 02/2023 - 02/2023

## Turkey

## 10/2022 - 12/2022 Gaza

# 09/2022 - present

Istanbul, Turkey

## 06/2022 - 09/2022

2022

Emirates

Khanyounes, Palestine

# Frontend Developer (React.js), Al-Qeeq Company [2]

• Responsible for developing interfaces for websites and dashboards.

## Frontend Developer

#### Dashboard

- Convert UI/UX using Bootstrap.
- Responsible for a responsive design.

## Frontend Developer

## Lawyers Dashboard

- Convert PSD using Bootstrap.
- Responsible for a responsive design.

## Frontend Developer

### Dashboard

- Convert UI/UX using Bootstrap.
- Responsible for a responsive design.

## React.js Developer, Ajyal Incubator

### Landing Page and Dashboard

- Responsible for building the UI using components.
- Using styled-components, bootstrap, reactstrap, ckeditor5-react.
- API integration using redux-thunk, and redux-saga.
- Applying responsive web design techniques.
- Working within a team.

## **Frontend Developer,** FoxyTech Company

## part-time

• Responsible for developing interfaces for websites.

# Frontend Trainer, Safi Design

## Frontend Development (70 hrs)

- HTML/ HTML5
- CSS/ CSS3
- JavaScript
- Bootstrap
- GitHub

### Frontend Developer, freelance-arabia

## **Project modification**

An Arab platform for freelance work.

- I worked on the project with a team on Github.
- Developed some pages and developed a chat page.
- Responsible for a responsive design.

#### 2022

## Frontend Developer, Mohtawa company

Kuwait

#### Website

An introductory website for a Saudi company working in the field of e-marketing and managing social media platforms.

- Developed the interfaces using Bootstrap.
- Responsible for a responsive design for all screens.
- Add animation to a website.

### 2021 - 2021

## Frontend Developer, Highnox

#### Sweden

#### Dashboard

Dashboard for the accountants' program.

- Convert UI/UX design to a perfect pixel dashboard.
- Using HTML, pure CSS.
- Use charts and the Drag and Drop technique.

#### 2021

## Frontend Developer, Krogarna.se

Sweden

#### Dashboard

A dashboard is special for selling courses so that free courses or for a fee are uploaded, and a certificate is given at the end of the course.

The interfaces of three sections of this dashboard have been developed, one for admin, one for employees, and one for students.

- Convert UI/UX using Bootstrap.
- Responsible for a responsive design.

### 2021

## Frontend Developer, Al-sharq Feloowship Program

Palestine

#### **Educational Website**

- Convert Figma design using Bootstrap.
- Responsible for a responsive design for all screens.

#### 2021

## React.js Developer, GGateway

#### Palestine

## ProShop Store

- Responsible for building the UI.
- API integration using React-redux.
- Using redux-thunk as a middleware.
- Responsible for the high performance of the website.
- Applying responsive web design techniques.



## **EDUCATION**

## 08/2015 - 12/2020

## BA, Al Quds Open University

Rafah, Palestine

Computer Information System



## SKILLS

- React.js
- CSS/3
- GitHub
- Styled-component
- React-Bootstrap

- React-redux
- Redux-toolkit
- HTML/5

JavaScript

Sass

• jQuery

• Bootstrap

D . . .

Responsive design

• API integration

- Redux-thunk •
- React-router
- React-hooks

## 3

## **LANGUAGES**

Arabic

English